Guide to the Stanford University, Queer Student Resources, Records SC0252
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- GPU/GLAS Records
  - Series II
    - Health and medical services [printouts from a database], 1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Legal aid services [printouts from a database], 1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Gay Men's Theater Collective (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Resources list from Amazon Quarterly, 1973 Sep (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Restricted files
      - Women's Counseling Collective (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Counseling (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Counseling - Fitch (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Counseling - Donna Aileen Coffin (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - David Hoefer (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Hingson - counseling (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Counseling & referrals - Donna Hughes-Oldenburg (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Counseling - Lessing (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Counseling - Lewis (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Counseling - Silverstein (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Counseling - Low (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Information requests (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Referral requests, or referrals made (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - The Gay Line, Reading, Calif. (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Mental Health Bureau - Santa Clara Co. emergency number (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - National Crisis Intervention Clearinghouse, publication of: National Exchange (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Youth Hot Line - National Runaway Switchboard (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Palo Alto info. and referral (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Palo Alto Area Info & Referral Service [PAAIRS] (& Peninsula Pregnancy Info. Collective) (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Parental Stress Hotline (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Santa Clara I & R [information and referral] (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Santa Clara County Information & Referral System. Resource manual, 1974 Apr (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Santa Clara County resources - Manuel input (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - 24 Hour Switchboard (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Suicide & Crisis phone line - Santa Clara County (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Suicide Prevention Center, San Mateo (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - Suicide Prevention Center of San Mateo County. Directory of Referrals and Resources., 1974 Nov (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Series III
    This series consists of the records of the Women’s Collective of GPU/GLAS. Materials found in this series relate to counseling, crisis line, meetings, projects. Formats include flyers, financial records, and correspondence.
    - Counseling/staff position: application of Sue Alexandre, 1974 Aug (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Women's Collective. Counseling/staff position: notes, publicity, correspondence, applications, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Rap topics/outlines (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Women's Collective. Crisis line: Proposal, contact sheets, calendars, memos, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Women's Collective. Crisis line: training collective, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Women's Collective: finances, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Wsomen's Collective. Minutes, 1976 Feb 24 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Women's Collective: special projects. Notes and correspondence, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Women's Collective. Weekly meetings, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Drolet, Jeannine "Lavender Troubadour", 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - GPU Women's Collective - correspondence: IN, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Women's Collective - Financial documents - ASSU statements of account, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Women's Collective - Misc., 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Women's Collective - Financial documents - ASSU check requests, deposit slips & journal transfers, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Women's Collective - Financial documents. Misc. invoices & purchase orders, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - GPU Women's Collective - Financial records, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - GPU Women's Collective - Correspondence, IN -- Commercial, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - GPU Women's Collective -- Correspondence, IN - Personal, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - GPU Women's Collective - Misc. documents and ephemera, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - GPU Women's Collective - Correspondence, IN - Organizations, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - GPU Women's Collective. Correspondence, IN. Commercial, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, IN - Personal, 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Women's Collective - Misc., 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, IN - Organizations, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Women's Collective - Correspondence, IN - Commercial, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Women's Collective - Correspondence, IN - Organizations, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Women's Collective - Internal communications, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Women's Collective. Posters and handbills, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - GLAS Women's Collective - Misc. records, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Women's Collective. Misc. records. Flyers/cultural resources, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - GLAS Women's Collective. Misc. records., 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Women's Collective. Financial records, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - GLAS Women's Collective. Misc. records, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Series IV
    This series contains the records of the Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week (GALA) committee, 1982-1985.
    - GPU-Gay Awareness Week, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Gay Awareness Week, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Gay Awareness Week, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week -- General documents, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week -- Specific events, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week - Program, general publicity and full poster, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week -- Gay Men's Chorus and Gay Family Day, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - GALA Week: Financial proposals, donations (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - GLAS GALA week publicity. Graphics of press releases, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - GALA Week events, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - GALA Week: Governor's Ball, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - GALA Week: General correspondence and internal communications, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - GALA Week advertising, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - GALA Week donations, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week: General correspondence and internal communications, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - GALA Week: funding (sponsors), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - GALA Week poster - text, graphics, materials, posters, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - GALA Week Program book: correspondence, memos, production material, typescript, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - GALA Week Progam book: master, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - GALA Week events, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - GALA Week T-shirts, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - GALA Week events, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Planning: GALA week, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Fundraising: GALA Week & Tee shirts, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Program book: GALA Week, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - GALA Week: to be refiled, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence IN - GALA Week, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence OUT - GALA Week, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Financial affairs - GALA Week, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Graphics - GALA Week, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Individual events - GALA Week, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Series V
    This series is made up of photocopies of the personal papers of certain students who were active in GPU/GLAS. The bulk of these personal papers represent personal correspondence, mostly incoming, though some copies of outgoing correspondence also exist.
    - David Abernethy - member of the GLAS Steering Committee (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Mike Brady - notebook (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Cuff, David. Misc. personal papers, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Brian Cheu - Notes re GLAS Archives Project, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jack Hamilton [notebook-papers] (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Noel Hanrahan - Misc. papers (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Noel's files: Noel Hanrahan - personal notes and files re activism, GLAS, etc. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Noel Hanrahan - Stanford course work with lesbian/gay/feminist content, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Noel Hanrahan - SWOPSI Policy Board materials, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Hiersch, Rhio - Misc. personal papers (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Hiersch, Rhio. Member of the GPU/GLAS Steering Committee. Notes re GPU/GLAS, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Hiersch, Rhio. Personal papers. SWOPSI 169: notes, drafts of course proposal, misc. documents, 1985 spring (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Hollars, Mike. Misc. papers and notes re involvement with GLAS (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Shaffer, Joy. Notes re Women's Collective, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Van Gaalen, Roland. GLAS Treasurer. Misc. personal notes re GLAS work. [served as treasurer 1984-86], 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Restricted files
      - Noel Hanrahan - Interview transcript [Candice Brown, interview subject], notes, draft of transexuality LFGB article, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Gerard Koskovich - Misc. personal papers. Stanford Daily Magazine annotated copy, 1986 Jan 24 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Stanford Daily - Valentine Personals. Gerard Koskovich - Misc. personal papers, 1986 Feb 14 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Steve Mandeville-Gamble. Personal papers: Family correspondence (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Steve Mandeville-Gamble. Personal papers: Stanford correspondence (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Series VI
    Contains posters, and the original artwork for these posters, 1978-1985. Also included are posters inscribed by the people, groups or organizations being announced by the posters, 1983-1986.
    - Gay Pride events: posters, flyers, calendar of events, banners [some defaced], 1979-1985 (Box 3, Box 1)
    - Gay People's Union at Stanford - Poster originals, 1978-1982 (Box 2)
    - Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford - Poster originals, 1982-1985 (Box 2)
    - Posters - inscribed copies, 1983-1986 (Box 2)
  - Series VII
    Includes assorted audiotapes and videocassettes of GPU/GLAS events and activities. Subjects include: news coverage of rallies and lectures, as well as conferences and interviews focusing on AIDS, homosexuality, pedophilia, and gay rights issues.
    - David Cuff - GALA Week interview. KZSU-FM (Stanford) "Face the Station", 1985 May 6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
    - Mark von Hagen - Homosexuality in the USSR, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
    - Western States Lesbian & Gay Students United. Panel discussion, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
    - First anniversary of Segal "Gay Liberation" sculpture installation, Lomita Mall, Stanford. Speakers: Mark Dupont, Jack Winkler, Noel Hanrahan, Phil Flint, 1985 Feb 21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
    - KZSU Campus Conference: "Homosexuality at Stanford.", 1986 May 12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
    - Rally on White Plaza in reaction to defacement of Segal sculpture. "Speak Out" to protest defacement., 1984 Mar 12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
    - Leonard Graff of National Gay Rights Advocates [NGRA] at GLAS. Intro by Jeff Golden of the Stanford Gay and Lesbian Law Students Association., 1984 Feb 22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
    - Gay and Lesbian Speakers' Bureau Presentation, Alpha Sig. Speakers: Mark Dupont, David Herrera, Elaine Holliman, Romney Robinson., 1984 Feb 29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
    - GLAS answering machine -- incoming messages: Segal death threat., 1984 Mar 8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
    - Dr. Edward Brongersma speaks on pedophilia: "Legan and social aspects of pedophilia: an international perspective." History Corner 034. Sponsored by GLAS and the Gay and Lesbian Law Students' Association., 1984 Mar 8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
    - 3 minute Stanford Cares mother introduction, 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
    - AIDS conference, 1986 Jan; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
    - Segal vandalism news conference, 1984 Mar; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
    - "Eroticizing Safe Sex" Workshop for GLAS by the Institute for the Advance Study of Human Sexuality, San Francisco, 1986 Jan; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
    - Update on AIDS - master (unfinished) Abram's lecture, 1985 Nov 20; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Series VIII
    Contains ephemera and miscellaneous items including a cloth banner, T-shirts, rubber stamps, poster masters, an office Rolodex file. This series also includes photocopies of Office of Student Activities files re GLAS, including Gay Community of Concern files.
    - Stanford Safe Sex Kits banner [painted on bedsheet], two "Out on the Farm" GLAS t-shirts (red, blue) (Box 1)
    - March on Washington button, 1979; GPU rubber stamps; poster masters; gay support group poster; 10 year awareness exhibit material, 1984; office Rolodex file, 1970s-1985 (Box 2)
    - Gay People's Union Scrapbook (photocopy as of May 1981), 1981 May (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Complaints to Stanford administration about gay events and activities on campus, 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Gay Community of Concern - grant proposal, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Gay Community of Concern - Misc. materials, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Gay Counseling Group, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Gay People's Union - Applications for University office space, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Gay People's Union - meeting with Campus Affairs staff, 1973 Oct 29 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Gay People's Union - non-discrimination policy proposal, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Gay People's Union - misc. correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Gay students - Misc. materials, 1974-1978 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Gay People's Union. Scholarship and loan fund proposals, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Gay Pride Week and Conference, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Sex in public restrooms - Police raids, arrests, Gay community response, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Gay People's Union. Funding request for Gay Awareness Week, 1979 May 7-13 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Motive magazine. v.32, no.2. One of two final issues of Motive, focusing on Gay Men's Liberation. Published by Methodist Student Movement., 1972 winter (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Article on Gay People's Union at Stanford from Vector magazine. v.8, no.9., 1972 Nov (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Roskovich, Gerald. "Out on the Farm," leaflet history., 1988 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Koskovich, Gerald. The Emergence of Gay and Lesbian Politics at Stanford University. Given as a talk at Rains House., 1989 May 11 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Gay Directory for the Media. Gay Coalition on the Media. [loose-leaf ring binder], 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Additional Records, 1983-1984; Accession ARCH-1983-171
  Gay and Lesbian Alliance at Stanford. Speakers Bureau questionnaires for dormitories.
  - Okada House survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1984 spring (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Florence Moore Hall survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1984 Apr 30 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Loro Speakers Bureau, 1984 Jan 23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Larkin House survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1984 May 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Trancos House survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1984 Feb 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ujamaa House survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1984 Jan 31 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Grove House, Phi Sig survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1983 Dec 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Toyon Hall survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1983 Nov 10 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Arroyo House survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1983 Nov 21 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Donner House survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1983 Nov 8 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - West Lagunita survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1983 Nov 8 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Soto House survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1983 Nov 3 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Burbank House survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1983 Nov 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Rinconada House survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1983 Oct 24 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Mirlo House survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1983 Oct 26 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Roble Hall survey of attitudes towards gay people, 1984 Apr 15 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1987-077
  - Misc. files (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Misc. files (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Misc. papers (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - IN - Misc., 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - IN - Misc., 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gavilan speaking engagement. Correspondence, 1981 Nov (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Peer Counselor training manual [published by The Bridge], 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Comments on magazines (ca. 73) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - David Morandi (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - PSA's [public service announcements] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Publications (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Stuff that we've written or mailed out (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Speaking log forms (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Stanford University Hierarchy - OSA, etc. Pre-1979 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Finances, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - RA letter (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - OSA, ASSU, S.U. Bureaucracy (1 of 2), 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - OSA, ASSU, S.U. Bureaucracy (2 of 2), 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Finances - ASSU #7391, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Bars (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Billy DeFrank Center (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Counseling (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Employment (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Gay Speakers Bureau (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Housing (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Mail (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Legal (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Medical (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Older gays (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Parents of gays (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Political (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Prisoners (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Professionals (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Referral agencies (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Religious (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Students (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Teachers (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Third World (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Transexuals (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Young gays (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Misc. materials (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Misc. mail and flyers (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Brochures and flyers from other organizations (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Gay info. & referral (notebook) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Lesbian I & R (info and referral) (notebook) file 1 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Lesbian I & R (info and referral) (notebook) file 2 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Lesbian I & R (info and referral) (notebook) file 3 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1995-234
  - Gay People's Union at Stanford - administrative records (including "a gay liberation reading list"), and event flyers (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2000-125
  - Subject Files
    - "AIDS Conscious" Saratoga, Ca (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - "AIDS Challenge: The Cost of Not Caring" Conference, Jan. 1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - AIDS Stanford misc. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - AIDS Peninsula/South Bay misc. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - ADHOC Task Force in Support of Innovative Academic Courses (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The Advocate (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - General documentation of Gay Men and Lesbians at Stanford (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Alexandrian Press (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Groups – non Stanford (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - American Institute for Safe Sex Practices (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - American Social Health Association (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - American Social Health Association newsletter: The Helper (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - American Social Health Association newsletter: The Hotliner (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Ames Research Center (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Apple Lambda (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - ARIS Palo Alto (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Asian American Activities Center (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - ASSU council of Presidents (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - ASSU Senate (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - ASSU Speakers Bureau (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Aurora Collective (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Bars Peninsula/South Bay (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Bath Houses Peninsula/South Bay (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Bay Area Lawyers for Individual Freedom (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Bay Area Municipal Elections Committee (San Jose) (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Beacon of Hope (Redwood City) (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Beyond Het. Stanfod student group (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Billy de Frank Lesbian and Gay Community Center newsletters, misc. (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Billy de Frank Lesbian and Gay Community Center newsletters, 1981-82 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Billy de Frank Lesbian and Gay Community Center newsletters, 1983- (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Billy de Frank Lesbian and Gay Community Center newsletters, 1985- (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Billy de Frank Lesbian and Gay Community Center newsletters, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Bisexuality Discussion Group (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Bisexual Support Group (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Black Community Issues Stanford (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Black Graduate Students Association (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Bookstores Peninsula/South Bay (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Boomer's (Redwood City) (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Bridge (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - B-Street/Sassys (San Mateo) (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Cable Car Awards (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - CA Alliance of Progressive Student Activities (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - CA Institute of Transpersonal Psychology (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - "California Week" Oct. 1986 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Calvary Metropolitan Community Church, misc. (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Career Planning and Placement Center (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Centennial Celebrations May 1987 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Center for New Beginnings (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Center for Research on Women (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - CIA Recruiting at Stanford (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - El Centro Chicano (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Child Advocacy Council Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Child Molesting news clippings (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Calvary Metropolitan Community Church newsletter (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Calvary Metropolitan Community Church newsletter (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Churches Peninsula/South Bay (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - College of San Mateo (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Communication Dept. (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - The Company (Stanford drama group) (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Concerts – Gay and Lesbian composers Peninsula/South Bay (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Contact/Dating Services Peninsula/South Bay (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Counselors (gay and lesbian) Peninsula/South Bay (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Cowell--Counseling & Psych. Services (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Cowell—The Student Body (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Cowell—women's health (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Cowell Student Health Center (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Dean of Student Affairs office AIDS Workshop (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - De Anza Community College (Cupertino) (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Different Spokes Cycle Club (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Doctoral Dissertations – Gay/Lesbian (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Doctoral Dissertations – Women's Studies (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Drama Dept. (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Drama Dept. – "The Normal Heart" (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Ellipse Peninsula AIDS Services (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Emerald City Cafe (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - English Dept. (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Estos Tempos Magazine Stanford (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Feminist Lesbian Social Group – Sunnyvale, CA (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Feldstar Stanford (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Feminist Studies Program (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Fiction (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Foothill Lesbian and Gay Students (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Force 5 Palo Alto (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Fraternities (articles) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Fundamentalist Preacher at Stanford (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - GLAAD (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Gala Realist Newsletter (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week Stanford (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Gay and Lesbian community directories (Box 2, Folder 9)